{
	"JavaQuestions" : {
		"1" : {
			"question" : "Which of the following is not a Java features?",
			"option1" : "Dynamic",
			"option2" : "Architecture Neutral",
			"option3" : "Use of pointers",
			"option4" : "Object-oriented",
			"answer" : "Use of pointers"
		},
		"2" : {
			"question" : "_____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
			"option1" : "JVM",
			"option2" : "JRE",
			"option3" : "JDK",
			"option4" : "JDB",
			"answer" : "JDB"
		},
		"3" : {
			"question" : "What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
			"option1" : "0",
			"option2" : "Not a Number",
			"option3" : "Infinity",
			"option4" : "Run time exception",
			"answer" : "Infinity"
		},
		"4" : {
			"question" : "Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?",
			"option1" : "It has only methods",
			"option2" : "Objects can't be created",
			"option3" : "It has a fixed class name",
			"option4" : "It has no class name",
			"answer" : "It has no class name"
		},
		"5" : {
			"question" : " In which process, a local variable has the same name as one of the instance variables?",
			"option1" : "Serialization",
			"option2" : "Variable Shadowing",
			"option3" : "Abstraction",
			"option4" : "Multi-threading",
			"answer" : "Variable Shadowing"
		},
		"6" : {
			"question" : "In which case, a program is expected to recover?",
			"option1" : " If an error occurs",
			"option2" : "If an exception occurs",
			"option3" : "Both of the above",
			"option4" : " None of the above",
			"answer" : "If an exception occurs"
		},
		"7" : {
			"question" : "What is the size of double variable?",
			"option1" : "8 bit",
			"option2" : " 16 bit",
			"option3" : "32 bit",
			"option4" : "64 bit",
			"answer" : "64 bit"
		},
		"8" : {
			"question" : "In which memory a String is stored, when we create a string using new operator?",
			"option1" : "Stack",
			"option2" : "String memory",
			"option3" : "Heap memory",
			"option4" : "Random storage space",
			"answer" : "Heap memory"
		},
		"9" : {
			"question" : "In java, jar stands for_____.",
			"option1" : "Java Archive Runner",
			"option2" : "Java Application Resource",
			"option3" : "Java Application Runner",
			"option4" : "None of the above",
			"answer" : "None of the above"
		},
		"10" : {
			"question" : "What of the following is the default value of an instance variable?",
			"option1" : "null",
			"option2" : "0",
			"option3" : "Depends upon the type of variable",
			"option4" : "Not assigned",
			"answer" : "Depends upon the type of variable"
		}
	}
}